=Revenge of Royal Princess=
= انتقام الأميرة الملكية =
=Episode 23=
= الحلقة 23 =
I knew you were my sister.
كنت أعلم أنك أختي.
But so what?
لكن ماذا في ذلك؟
You still didn't take me seriously.
ما زلت لا تأخذني على محمل الجد.
Li Xie.
لي شيه.
You are my dear brother since childhood.
أنت أخي العزيز منذ الصغر.
Do you know what you're talking about?
هل تعرف ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟
Sister.
أخت.
Look.
ينظر.
Back then,
في ذلك الوقت،
the current situation was turbulent,
كان الوضع الحالي مضطربًا ،
you helped me ascend the throne with your own strength.
لقد ساعدتني في اعتلاء العرش بقوتك.
But you raised Han Shu step by step.
لكنك قمت بترقية هان شو خطوة بخطوة.
Do you know how scared I am?
هل تعلم كم أنا خائف؟
Sister.
أخت.
I miss you so much, sister.
اشتقت لك كثيرا يا اختي.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
You got the wrong person.
لقد حصلت على الشخص الخطأ.
Sister, sorry.
أخت ، آسف.
Only when you are dead can I truly love you.
فقط عندما تموت يمكنني أن أحبك حقًا.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
Only the blood sacrifice of Xie Yugui
فقط تضحية الدم من Xie Yugui
can the people of the country be protected
يمكن حماية شعب البلد
and Royal Princess be rest in peace.
والأميرة الملكية ترقد بسلام.
No matter you are Xie Yugui or Li Yanchu,
لا يهم أنك Xie Yugui أو Li Yanchu ،
you have to stay in this tomb forever.
عليك أن تبقى في هذا القبر إلى الأبد.
I thought that as long as you left,
اعتقدت أنه طالما غادرت ،
I would be able to firmly hold the country.
سأكون قادرًا على الاحتفاظ بالبلد بحزم.
But you left me Han Shu,
لكنك تركتني هان شو ،
the one I hate the most.
أكثر ما أكرهه.
Sister.
أخت.
You are never softhearted.
أنت لست أبدا رقيق القلب.
Why is he an exception?
لماذا هو استثناء؟
Li Xie.
لي شيه.
Is that what you think of me?
هل هذا ما تعتقده عني؟
Sister.
أخت.
You could have lived a few more days.
كان من الممكن أن تعيش بضعة أيام أخرى.
But you got too close to him.
لكنك اقتربت منه.
So you have to die.
لذلك عليك أن تموت.
So it was you
لذلك كنت أنت
who poisoned me?
من سممني
You hate me that much?
أنت تكرهني كثيرا؟
Sister used her life to let me be loyal to you.
أخت استخدمت حياتها لتسمح لي أن أكون وفية لك.
But you poisoned her?
لكنك سممتها؟
Li Xie.
لي شيه.
Good for you.
هنيئا لك.
You played a trick on me
لقد لعبت خدعة علي
even before I died.
حتى قبل وفاتي.
And I am so stupid.
وأنا غبي جدا.
I thought we loved each other.
اعتقدت أننا نحب بعضنا البعض.
So I did everything
لذلك فعلت كل شيء
to keep you safe.
للحفاظ على سلامتك.
But it's still no match
لكنها لا تزال غير متطابقة
for your jealousy.
لغيرتك.
So what are you going to do?
ماذا ستفعل؟
Kill me
اقتلني
for Han Shu?
لهان شو؟
Or do you want to be an empress?
أم تريد أن تكون إمبراطورة؟
Li Xie.
لي شيه.
I love you
أحبك
and protect you.
ويحميك.
Yet you never understood me.
ومع ذلك أنت لم تفهمني أبدا.
I never wanted the throne.
لم أرغب أبدا في العرش.
I wish you
اتمنى لك
a long life
حياة طويلة
on your icy dragon throne.
على عرش التنين الجليدي الخاص بك.
The Regent sought power to usurp the throne
سعى الوصي إلى السلطة لاغتصاب العرش
and held Princess Yong'an hostage.
واحتجزت الأميرة يونغان رهينة.
Take him down now,
انزله الآن ،
no matter he's alive or dead.
بغض النظر عن أنه حيا أو ميتا.
Come someone!
تعال شخص ما!
Hunt them down!
اصطيادهم!
(The right of communication through network)
(حق الاتصال عبر الشبكة)
(exclusively belongs to Tencent.)
(تنتمي حصريًا إلى Tencent.)